tales like they were survival guides be the princess smile obey wait fear the
villain never ask why then life got its hands on the story and every page caught
fire
They dressed the truth in ribbons and lace,
Called it hope with a prescylin face,
Said if I stay quiet some day I'll be found,
That a perfect little smoker turned the world around,
But castles crumble, crowns collect dust,
Promises fade when they're built on trust,
I watch the heroes ride right past,
While the ones who survive understand at last.
From from Shatterj,
Just someone who refused to reign,
Trying to make red as pain,
But I learned voices often fear,
The only speech is bad,
Later smiles for the spotlight,
Poison for the neighbors,
Time and again you reach
On my throat, bunch of words would sink me, instead they kept me afloat
Every sky like every bruise is building up the roof, doesn't matter, sit the ground
Voices always crack beneath the weight, building castles, gossip, wondering why they never stay
Ending heavy light runs out of breath, steady, it survives, what kills the rest?
Tumors in every sheet, keep your kingdom tumbled down
Come in and fix this
Love without a clue
How you like me when they tell
We want to call the star
Baby love is looking for love
She wants some money
She's so intro
Daddy ain't around
So she just turns back to the crowd
We go her up
She fly high and see it
Never coming down
They don't know
Uh huh
You aren't just so fucking s**t, it's not my fault that I'm so f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g f*****g
And I'm gonna play you in my new state, always, always, always, always, always, always, always.
So, how are we doing?
Um, the day of the Tuesday.
It's almost Tuesday.
Four minutes.
I still got, like, half of the celebs.
I don't even drink very much.
I have, like, maybe one or two a day.
Several days a week.
It's not about that.
I have this blinker too, or this, uh, bait, but this one's really hard to hit.
It's okay though.
Hi Nancy, you just woke up?
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, what a day.
I mean, it's kind of a crazy day.
You know, we got people losing their minds everywhere
and it's like, you know, it's really evident.
I mean, I mean, I'm gonna have to go through some
of the timeline with this crazy situation,
but I think I should just leave it on the,
oh, there's something pending right now.
I'm just gonna leave it alone for a minute,
but yeah, there's a, you know.
People just going pretty low, you know, I guess the other day, you know Brandon who like, you know
several weeks ago I
We had the falling out. I have had on the show since to kind of like, you know
Let him show his ass, which means I can bear with some so
You know, he's he lies. He like he weaponizes people and the whole thing was I could guess a couple weeks ago
You know he wanted to come on Alex's panel cuz salmon was there this is how like a chain reaction happens
Right because everything was fine. I mean Alex, you know Alex had an I and X and me and Brandon
We were her top three
We were like in our top three three BFFs
You know replaced Tricia Licious and stroke off in Q and you know chicken cakes and
You know the hundred other people you know Zand every I mean all the other people we were we were friends
We were friends for a little bit again. I mean I've had the I had I went through the cycle before
Um, that day, like, she's like,
oh, okay, well, and she just didn't want him up
the same time as Sam, and she was gonna let him up anyway, but.
And then he like goes onto his own show.
He's like, oh, that bitch, you know,
she just needs to pay me a thousand dollars
if she ever wants to be my friend again.
And, and I went over there because she was like,
oh, can someone go check on him,
making sure he's not freaking out
and to tell him not to say something he regrets or something.
I went over there.
He's already talking to INX.
And so that was it.
I left it at that.
I did talk to them on the show that day.
And I was like, hey, chill.
As I was like, you know, she's a good friend.
I just had hope that she had, you know, had sand he left, you know, but, uh, but anyway,
so then that night she posted this video and she's like Karen has a voicemail that says
.
You know beat it wasn't trying to kill me with psyche trying to set me up. So this is like what?
What?
.
What is this coming from? Okay?
Weird and I guess she well, so I didn't even know what I was like. What's going on? I texted her. I was like
.
I was like what's going on like, you know?
I was like, no, something just happened.
We had it falling out before, I'll tell you why.
You see her in Sam & Zerler?
Yeah, I mean, it's like, wow, talk about musical chairs.
I mean, it's like a hate party and stuff.
And it's like, I know, maybe it's a thing
that we've all done at one time or another,
but it's like, it never feels clean doing that.
And it's like, those aren't very good foundations
for true friendships.
And then it's like, they'll turn on you once,
they'll turn on you again.
That's a good lesson.
But anyway, yeah, she was here, but Nancy went to her chat
because she was today, she was addressing me
by not my name, but by my mother's name.
You know, saying, oh, the son of,
and then my mother's name.
You know, and then I guess she's mad.
She might be mad because Brandon, again, Brandon, right?
Brandon.
When I had him up he flashed a picture. It was just a black guy with the red ball in his mouth
But I was like, I don't know who that is
Could possibly be her father's and I don't know who put her all the nursing and picturing thing. So
I I kicked them off from the stage immediately. I actually took care of it
I mean, it's like which I'll do it's like, you know, if it's people's families or you know
Or kids or something like that. I and it's like I because I don't I
Mean, there's all the docs that I've been accused of what but for showing Christine's picture for making up
Or for putting that thumbnail beta that I took down immediately when she talked to me and and apologize
And then she struck me because it was in a trip kick video and stuff. Hmm. I mean
Now beat is you know cozy up to her now that now they're teaming up against I and X. They're like, oh, well
Oh, you know, I can't believe I am I next said you do coke Alex
Can't believe it. I don't know I next knows a lot. She knows a lot. I mean, she does get all the
People just like like to tell her every cell, you know her things and so sure
I don't know. She's been smart to actually like record some of these these voicemails and stuff because
People are such liars. I mean, it's like and where's any of this evidence to back up anything any of the stuff
She's telling me and then it's not only that now. She's like saying oh well
I'm uh and she and Brandon are the they're basically the same person. They're very very similar
That's why they just like they like they like smacked it. They got together real quick, right also
Brandon like I had a falling out with him and that and she was like well
I you know she's like I'm gonna talk to him tomorrow
And she's like oh no and she works over so old friends and stuff
But you know what's that you just keep it separate just don't have them on your show and stuff
I was like sure and no problem and then
But it was like three days later all that shit happened. It's a little bit crazy. She's being a big phony. I mean you can just but it's like
I just kind of see how I set up in the second part of the relationship and I can I'm gonna get a show
Her first appearance after we ruck in style. She came to my show one night
We had talked earlier in the night and she was kind of intoxicated
But she's like I want to go on your show and so I was like, okay. Well, come on up. And so this was half this happened
Think it was like right before Easter. No, sorry, but no, it's probably right after Easter, you know, and she was you know
She's right. She said she's I mean she's she I'm not thinking anything. She doesn't said she's she said she had sent me like
you know flowers and gifts and and
You know said really nice things and and you'll see how she like you know changes up the story here and she actually says
She was wrong and you know, she's a sorry and she Paul. So this is like so I just want before anybody else gets
Trapped up in the cycle with some of these wackos. I mean, it's like Brandon Q and her. I mean, it's like geez
I wish can they just have a baby together and like you know being on the island
Preferably, you know Epstein's Island never never seen again by Americans. I mean, I don't know. Okay. Hold on a second
So this was the the live
When I came back
Started on this channel. Hold on and she came on one night and it was
Let's just say it was interesting, but also she was you know, she's hate bonding with RG tonight had him on her panel
Oh RG come up come up come up, and then he is oh is anyone called his parents?
Yeah, I mean, this is just you're right. It's like so I used to I've had
I've been harassed by people before before you know that the call my house and right then we know how to deal with this kind of things
See we're much more tight knit than
people might think because I do keep it separated, but it's like you know
And also, I was very, she's talking about,
you know, my father passed away like three years ago,
her father passed away last year,
my father passed away a little over two years ago.
And so, and her, and so,
I'm also still in a grieving process.
I know I'm a little, maybe a year ahead of her,
because, you know, and we are both,
and our both are fathers, I'm gay,
but her father was gay, and it's,
and then it's like, you know,
both of our fathers had cancer and stuff,
and died around the same time of year and stuff.
So we bond trauma bonded hate bonded over that maybe I think she said I am using you
I'm using you because I want to know more about you know gay men because my father go and you know
Was all friendly and good. I mean when it's good. It's good. It was like when it's good. It was never bad
It was always good. That's the problem with like when things are always good
Because things are never always good there needs to be some kind of negativity or like some kind of but I was some of the second
Time I was walking on eggshells, but I didn't want to intentionally
I didn't want to just like piss her off because the first time she got mad at me was because I didn't like
It's AI she did of me
where I was like, you know, had this like stealing money from banks with the cats and stuff like that.
I was like, I didn't get it. I was like, I said, are you turning on me?
She's like, how dare you think that? And then she turned on me. I mean, it's like, and then I was
spiritual trafficker, and I was, I mean, a million terrible, terrible things. But, you know,
I still had an affection for her. And I mean, he got to it. It got kind of ugly. I mean, she was doing AIs of me, you know,
Humping Tommy James in a bed and not the cute, you know, juggalo version of like, you know, with the nice, you know
The nice body and the boxers and the the muscles. No, no, she had me with the fat old junkie James
No jam company involved
Anyway, so where is the stream with her?
And she asked me actually she actually asked me to delete the stream. She's like, oh, I don't think you should play that one
So I kept it
Okay, something like this happened, which I knew I would
So that thing's really a surprise. It's just like interesting to see how
Accurate I am down to the day. I knew what would happen. I
Don't know why still I did ask her why and she said you know what you did
Does anybody like when people say that?
You know what you did and it's like I know what you did less. There's a whole there's a whole prank that you can do
It's like calling people and you can say
You know just called call somebody as a prank. You say I know what you did
And they'll say, what do I do?
Like, what?
And then their mind will start going to all the bad things
they did, right?
And, right?
And so then those aren't naming things.
And then you all of a sudden have all this information.
But when you have a good, you know, I mean, I really,
I mean, I've had, who do I have a past?
Not really a bad past.
I've been very like, you know.
Kind of a sucker in the past sometimes and I'm kind of easily manipulated too nice too forgiving
I mean, I haven't done mean things to people unless they've really fucking gone after me, which some people have right, but
try to keep it kosher
but
But the shit is getting too crazy. Okay, so here's the episode so we can go and we can go through it
Okay, let's have a look at this episode. I'll start when she gets here
In the thing. I was playing like this one. I was playing the ugly duckling and stuff and you can see
How is everyone doing? Hi one Chubbard
Yeah, she's always flip flop
Dead fish or not her life. Hold on. Here we go. Watch this
Well, uh, they went talk to good times. Have you seen good times? Good times supposedly got a DUI or something last night and
Oh, yeah, I was gonna say Nancy went in and it was why are you why are you bringing his mom into it?
And she goes get the fuck out of here you bitch and stuff like that. She was like fuck you bitch
That's what she literally if she didn't even say it. She typed it in
It was so rude all dancing to without the question Nancy's been supportive of her
You know it's like so I mean just as an example of how she treats people so
I'll put it. Yeah, there's Ms. Lenore.
Maybe I can walk with you to McDonald's and like your coffee.
But I feel bad just going there to get a refill and stuff.
Fuck, baby.
I was tired in the bar, but I still went on.
Oh, they're gonna be standing with me.
You know, Alex donated.
McQueen, if you donated something.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, that's okay.
May I have a song?
Hello. Hello. How are you doing? Pretty good. Not so beautiful at this moment. I probably look
really fucked up, to be honest with you. Well, you look better than me. I look like I just rolled
out a bed, don't I? Yeah, but you're a guy. It's different. It's different. You look like Jesus
A modern day, I don't know,
Jared Leto rock star kind of vibe.
It works for you.
Thank you.
Yeah, my hair is pretty much,
I think the most it's ever been.
It's like.
I mean, it's not that long, really.
Cause you have the little curly cues and whatnot, don't you?
Yeah. I wish it like came out like, you know,
it's just beautifully straight.
Maybe I can do that.
Well, no, no, not straight.
I like the curliness.
If anyone comes up on the stream and I don't want to talk
to him and let you know right now, I'm going to depart.
I want your help with the selfish matter.
Okay, you know, I'll let you know. Yeah, I'm live. Oh, yeah. Okay. I'll tell you why. But if you want to come up and talk, I'll pause this.
My loneliness is killing me because it is. This lady's turned on me. I didn't realize that till today. But it is. And that's why I'm so grumpy.
My own like, you know, kind of even like with everybody or even with people around kind of like alone, you know, like
I'm a little bit less lonely than me. I would say
I have these cats and so the cats like three cats. Well, did tricks what happened with tricks?
Tell me the tricks update because I'm not worried about that. My followers know that
Yeah, well tricks tricks it's tricks back like where's tricks the trick
And I have a, you know, a notice in the next door with a really good photo of him.
He has a distinct little freckling on his nose and stuff, which is like,
we'll make it easy to identify.
Well, he's a gray striped cat, right?
He's white and he has like, I'll put a picture of him.
Let me see.
I have a picture of him.
This is a picture.
Yeah, put a picture.
Because, yeah, because I think you're thinking of his mom, like Lola, like Tricks here is right here.
Set up, you can see how long.
It's not the best picture of me, but here.
Aw, hey Tricks.
Okay, okay, Lenore, my spirit animal, I suppose.
Defending you from my sexual energy.
Is that what it is? Is that what it is? Because it is a little bit potent. I am a little potent.
I've realized that over the past few years.
Yeah, well...
Yeah, let me put you on my channel, Cult of Psyche.
Why are you tracking me into your cult, which I'm not necessarily opposed to? What's going on with your ass?
Oh, well, it's like, um, I don't, I always consider the cult the cult of two and like,
you know, that was, well, I did like, but it's like, he's nightmares, that's what you're
calling it.
The nightmares, really?
I'm looking at it right now, nightmares on Elm Street.
Really, really, really, really, maybe on the lane of street?
Is that okay?
Uh-huh.
She just can't resist to dox everything.
Look, I'm going to be the real asshole in your life.
You don't want to be LGBTQ, okay?
Well, let's let it be.
I'm going to be the asshole.
I'll tell you what happened.
Hold on a second.
In that world, even though I'm not really...
Well, what happened is...
we were friends like I guess from like last year for like three months and then
And we're supposed to do this Christmas holiday special together and then she like turned on me got all mad for no reason really
Three months of just slandering and fighting with each other doing meme wars
She put up like memes of me like burning in a fire being burned by like Lilith and
Yeah, what else you know on a cross basically, I mean just really bad stuff and I for every gave her we were friends with her in three months
Why did she turn on me? Well the second like because we had like these mutual friends and then
one's kind of this controversial guy and
He you know, he got mad at her one day and then
All of a sudden she said it was my fault that she met him and stuff, yeah, yeah, then we do the memes
I mean, it's like I did a meme of her because you know
She has a she kind of like you know kind of a more well-known porn star back in like 2010
She had sex with Lexie and steel and stuff and she was in she was in the she was a police
Arashad's part in the the Cosby show porno. I know I've anyone seen that but
You know I guess and I talked to her once she said the most offensive thing I ever said was that she was
Dp'd because she said she was never Dp'd. She only did sing because she only did was regular penetrated by one person and
Little bit of lesbos stuff
But I think it was like kind of simulated because it was like it doesn't seem like she was really looking anything and then she would also
Oh, yeah, she would peg guys too. So she would fuck guys
And I'll I'll I will say she did you know, I wasn't I wasn't in the top through probably two or three for
sperm sperm donor
Request, you know, she was making she was sort of asking but then she started asking a lot of guys and I was like, okay
I don't know. I don't know about this. I don't know. So okay
My sperm is just safe. Let's just put it that way. Yeah
She does it to everybody. She's she's now but now she's going too far. She's she's saying I'm like, you know
I'm in a drug extortion ring sending meth through the mail
Yeah
Hey, hey Nancy, this is God buddy. Have you seen it? Have you met God buddy? I don't know if she's been to your chat
But yeah, he's awesome. I just
He has a membership program and I recommend everyone check that out and check out his channel.
I can post it.
Yeah, my sperm is now safe.
And I mean, it's like, I mean, one time in a good time, I had asked him after we...
Broke apart as friends and she's I said broke up once she was like I can't regain him
I broke up her as friends and he said well
She asked me for my sperm and wanted out with my baby and then I said well
She's and then she said well when you meet the baby
And I was like when it can talk and I kind of a conversation with it
And then she got mad because she wanted him to help raises or something
Thank you. Yeah, she's still oh my god. It gets worse and worse every day
I can't even like today it got really really bad because she was she got into like a lot of personal information
that it's like, yeah, maybe it's, you know,
in a form of public source, but it's,
she only got it because, you know,
she knew some of my personal information
and maybe, because I met her in person,
I maybe disclosed, you know, trusting, you know,
it was bad, bad decision, you know,
but she doesn't need to go and say, oh,
Like my parents are terrible people and like what and making fun of my mom and my dad my dad's passed away and stuff
And then her dad's passed away
And so she should understand like you don't put pictures of my parents up and stuff. It's not sick bullshit, right?
really, it's a bullshit and
and worse like I mean actually have I have like the list of things she called me on her show and
It's quite a list. I mean, it's like a long list. I mean, I mean, I wish it wasn't okay, so
But I will tell you, um, okay, so there's personal attacks. Okay, so it says.
She, there's public identification of my family.
So it says, my parents' names, the discussion of their home
and their house and their business
and where they live and the family history
and of their children and of their money.
The transcript references material taken from a,
it was from a magazine interview from several years ago.
So it says that the accompanying video
is played photographs, which it did.
So she was showing the video, it's photographs too.
And then it says, heavy reliance on speculation.
Many statements are clearly framed as speculation rather than supported facts.
Examples include speculation about my upbringing, family dynamics,
my parents' opinions, my employment history, drug use, mental health,
motivation, finances, criminality, family relationships, racial attitudes, and sexuality.
Numerous questions are posed rhetorically.
What went wrong? Maybe. Could it be? I wonder.
These questions are by viewers toward negative conclusions without presenting,
supporting evidence within the transcript. Then it gets to the personal attacks.
The transcript contains repeated insults directed at me. Examples include describing me as a monster,
a demon, criminal, abusive liar, exploitative, greedy, vindicative, vindictive, malicious,
decrepit, problematic son, and a failure.
Serious allegations include that I exploit grieving people, exploit mentally ill people,
exploit elderly people, emotionally exploit viewers, financially exploit viewers, black male
people, extort people, encourage suicide, bully women, seek personal information for later abuse,
committed a crime involving recording a phone call, use drugs, refuse to work, and rely on my
and speculates about my parents, siblings,
family, wealth, business, parenting, ability.
She also discusses race, family, servants,
if I had a mammy, cosmetic surgery,
possible racism, and my sexual orientation.
And that has nothing to do with the magazine.
So she said she wasn't gonna.
So anyway, that's it.
You know, pretty terrible, right?
Punisher?
Hey, that's what I'm doing right now, dude.
That's what I'm doing right now.
I'm gonna play in this.
She wanted me to delete this one,
but I was like, I'm gonna play this
and remind you what you do.
Into that world. That's what that's what pissed me off about your friend ghost really didn't did you hear my own
Rant. Oh shut the fuck up. He's going after me. You know
Enjoyed it. Okay. I listened to that. I was in the two episodes kind of big
But it was a really rant. It was really good coverage of like, you know, probably one of like the first like debate like real debates almost like
I didn't get to talk that day. I got upset about that
Yeah, he talks over everybody and then he's very rude and you know, so I'm gonna
I tried to kick him off the time
Don't reprimand him. I mean, you know, you can say whatever you want to say
Look at Lenore I
Should have been
Somebody's human. I think you would I think you're more than a cat daddy. You know, they got a good farmer here
around you and
What not?
It's just like, you know, I'm like
What's you are you're very
Not all the time
But I'm just this is my show. This is what you do on my show. So I'm allowed to talk people say I stop
I'm stalking people because I talk about
But I'm not doxing your whole family and talking about it
Yeah, look at this
I'm publicly acknowledging
See you put me through some stuff, but what I'm um
Triggered your insecurity. I should have been born a male in
award time
Probably two generations ago. I would be very good at it. She kept telling me what you want to be a white man and stuff
Yeah, sorry. Yeah
Oh, you're sorry? Thank you. Thank you so much. I am. I'm very sorry because I have all this.
And it's a weapon and it shouldn't be, but it is. But I'm sorry because I had to beat you down a
I'm sorry, but you survived. Somehow.
I survived. I survived.
Thank you, Joe. I think you put up a good fight.
And then it's like at the end of the day.
Well, you, you, you did it. Well, not just like, I mean,
the ending was you didn't deserve certain things.
Yeah, it got a little bit ugly, but I had to learn how to laugh at myself, you know.
Even in the memes.
He got to where I was like, you know, she had me fucking her.
Like this guy she likes in an AI video.
I mean, it's like, and I was like, anybody I'm attracted to.
And stuff like that.
I guess that's what she said, she's saying that.
But yeah, and then it's like,
and when it started eating really,
and she started doing me like all bald,
like look at the picture she does of me.
Hold on, I'll show you this picture.
I'm gonna see this picture, and God body.
God body is a gorgeous bald man, right?
And so I like bald men,
but look, she made me like an ugly bald.
Look at this, this is supposed to be me.
I'm far right here.
That's what she, that's what she has at me.
Isn't that crazy?
It's fucking crazy.
Yeah, but see and see that's me and that's like I mean it's like so these are all other people involved and stuff like that
With like, you know, she now she you know hates all these people
This is like but uh, but she makes them all look good and she I look terrible
Like terrible. I mean, it's like I don't have my shirt open my pajama pants hike so high
You know with my my head is not bald like that. I would like
Thank you. Well, thank you. You crack you crack me up, too. You're he's really fun
Oh my gosh guys, you got to check out his channel and stuff because he uh, he's he like talks to his chat
And he like and at one time I like I hid somebody because I said like pretty much something terrible
He's like no, he's like I don't hide. He doesn't hide people. He can deal with the trolls
He'll go toe-to-toe with them
It's just like I have no more energy to I mean, I just got I just had so I basically my whole community was trolls.
And so it's like, it got too annoying, you know, it's like, and I just like, and I got also they went real life on me
and like sent stuff to my house and people in my house and stuff all the time.
And so, uh, yeah.
Okay, so I forgot what I was going to show there, but here I'll take it down.
Okay.
Okay, I'll put this back up.
You can I'm going to get your channel.
I'll post your channel right now.
Hold on.
There we go.
I was like, well, at least I'm gonna be...
Well, you're tough yourself. I mean, you beat the shit out of me, man.
Well, I'm sorry.
You did.
I always want to, like, more, like, you know, feel like it's a friendly thing.
Even, like, you know, if there's public things going on, like, it'd be, like, at least, like, to, like, kind of, like, be...
I don't have the understanding, you know, otherwise.
Well, how are you going to be?
Are you going to be called to psych, like you're waking?
Yeah, but it's like really bad the intense of your house
I'm gonna let you know right I have any of God monetized at this time. Oh my gosh
Well, I don't know if you're doing you see do you see the Rajneesh video? Oh, I don't know
I don't know anymore. You did not see it like it's a tripping kick tripping kick made it
And I don't know if you ever watch that, but I don't know if there's a new channel
Oh, the one with the whole whole thing going on
You just want to like just watch
Fighting on the show.
In a different way.
I mean, I feel like I have to go up against, um...
Here's his shirt.
What's that guy's name?
Ghost?
He hates me, so I'm going to have to completely obliterate him, but I love God, or Gotti.
He's my favorite.
Well, she destroyed Gotti, too.
I mean, how am I going to destroy a cult if Gotti, or God, is a part of this?
Well, let me try to maybe I can summon him. I'm not sure I get I do I do have a means to like, you know
Maybe I I I want to know what it looks like so bad yet
I don't want to know because it's such a mystery
well head to where she's like talking to RG because it got really ugly here and
Be your discretion is advised and you know, you can tell she's a black woman, so she's allowed to say the word but
I mean this, I'm not just like, oh, drama, whatever.
No, I'm serious.
I'm serious, I won't.
I mean, it's like, you know, I just like.
Well, stop it.
Because, you know, there's a lot of people.
I meant the channel, but my-
Including me, who care about you.
And this whole thing is just too much.
Yeah, but like if you want to say
I'm depressed. I'm gonna go to sleep for three days. Okay fine. Go to sleep for a few days
But this whole thing
She's a drunk. He's having a week. Yeah
I mean, what okay? Let me ask you a question. What is what if I feel suicide?
What if I want to kill myself?
Right now
No, let's not know how are you gonna feel?
I don't feel horrible, and I would, you know, I would be sad.
Well, what if I decided to do it?
No, I would be sad.
But what if I'm just sitting here thinking to myself, well, I'm less than three years
away from 15.
Yeah.
I'm getting sad.
I got love handles in my hand, you know, what am I going to do?
It is good.
It is bad as well.
I don't look so great.
I might have had a stroke.
Is that why half of my face feels like it's like drooping, like, like, what's happening?
I don't know, I feel like an alcoholic.
Well, let me drink a little bit.
Would you like to talk to RG?
He's back soon.
So RG was seems like a reason to kill myself.
I've got no kids, got no lover, got no nothing.
I already worked out my will.
But she's not just buddy.
But I know where I'm at.
I want hugs and kisses too.
So it's like I could anyone get hugs and kisses.
Think about it.
Well, he's gonna tell me to kill myself. Yeah, put him on here. I didn't tell you that I wouldn't do that
Well, I find you very amusing
One of the best shows on it on YouTube
Did you really have a stroke I hope not
The healthy Alex is good for everybody. No, he's telling me to kill myself. Go ahead. I did not tell you to do that
Stop putting words my mom. No, go ahead. I hope you live to be a hundred and twenty years old
No, you're a white piece of trash. Go ahead. Wow. Don't forget the juice stuff
Ah, there's that look you're not quite smart enough to be a jail
Like you Alex see there's that that mischievous smile you're fucking hammered, huh? Wow
You're done talking about
No, go ahead
No, you already did you are absolutely did not what do you say in regards to
I like Tommy man, I wish the best for him
Right you think he's above me
If you guys could make you each other happy that I would be all for it. I would never talk to him again my life
Tell the truth. Why is what a Tommy do that was so horrible to you?
Tell the truth about what you think about I just did of a living garbage
You think Tommy's a piece of living garbage?
Why is that, Alex?
Because you were very drunk in this one two weeks ago.
Oh, well, yeah, obviously.
And then now it's really.
I am being nice, chat.
You like to share the people expected right now.
Say what you really think about me, KKK.
Remember, say it.
Kkk member
No, that's you get my show you can't get me fired off my own show
You can get me kicked off rumble, baby
No, I can't get you fired from where your money comes from
That is where my money comes from
No, your brother and sister too. Oh
Well, that's no you could probably get them fired. Hey Steve Pokemon show come check it out and rubble. We do political commentary
Have you as a guest? No, that's not the right name. You can come do your insight
No, I know where you live and I know your siblings
But oh no, why do you gotta always threaten people? Why can't you be nice?
You just said you're gonna have my brothers and sisters fired. I am. Yes, that's right
You're a smart woman. You know the definition
That's true. You wish you would make a great amazing guess on the Steve Pokemon show
That's not who you are
Then who am I?
Dun-dun-dun, huh?
Not like like yeah, you know a face of like a like like I want to say if you had a dog
I bet it would look exactly like him
Like one of those
Maybe you're close up. No, I would be I've been told that
It's all I look exactly like pickles to bleep be quite honest
People's fucking adorable lady. I know you have hate in your heart, but you can't hate this dog. You just can't do it
I don't hate any animals. I just hate all see I knew there was something at least one thing that's about you Alex
I'm trying so hard to be nice to you
Why won't you just embrace it Alex?
You're a beautiful human inside and out
You're really your porn career was very boring, but besides that you seem like a wonderful nice person
No, I'm not the poor thing wasn't for you though. It was quite a poor
Didn't watch Alex Marry porn be quite honest with you
I'm your worst nightmare if I could no no you're an old lady. Who's you?
I would pull the trigger.
You're a fucking over-the-hill lady who never had a child or a husband.
And you take out all the frustration on random YouTubers.
That's what you do.
Apparently you just had a stroke.
Because I can see the droopiness now that you mentioned that you had a stroke.
I can see it.
What about like massage therapy or something?
No, I'd rather just put the gun to your head and pull the gun.
Do you sleep next to the air conditioner because you can like reverse at it?
No?
Okay.
Well, it's a shame that you're, you know, it's a shame, you know, you had a stroke in
your face.
I know.
So what's your five-year plan, Alex?
Do you plan on always being a mythical cunt?
I actually plan to seek you out, find you.
Okay.
Good.
I know, yes
Yeah, you worry you'll you'll worry about
Don't worry about crazy ladies on the internet. I just really don't
I know you get off on people being scared of you though. I find that very funny
You know, well, I don't mind why bombs are like, oh, no, it's Alex mayors.
Oh, everybody, everybody be scared of the Alex mayors.
I don't, I don't know.
You're not going to get that with me.
You're not going to get that with me, sweetie.
I hate to tell you.
I know you're very good.
It's Bojangles.
Everybody be scared of the Alex mayors.
Overly amplified microphone volume.
Wait, hold on.
You want a Nazi to knock you off, really?
That can't be true. I'm reading chat.
You know, I'm not listening to you.
Well, chat.
I love Alex. I love Alex.
I have a better communication voice than you do, Alex.
Face it. I have a better voice for broadcasting than you do.
The volume is too loud.
Alex, I have a better broadcasting voice than you do, and you know it.
You're a better broadcasting voice than you do admit it
Okay, that's fair. I think I could kill you and get away
Admit that I have a better broadcast
Before that's interesting do tell do tell
Why listen Alex the audience is intrigued they want to hear more
I admit that I have a better broadcasting voice than you
Know you think you have the best bracket. I have not you. I am superior as far as it comes to broadcasting voices
miss Alex
You know just so I can get all scared
Look at the alcohol got herself. I'm sorry. I didn't see her miss me that I'll be really scared if you give me a proximate location
Look how evil she got I just I love it so much. You are one of my favorite
You are I'm your dad
No, you can scare like wine moms and stuff, you know scared me. I just think you're a sad lonely old woman
Unlovable unlovable somewhere
You're not capable of love receiving it. We're giving it
Are you my dad mommy if I was your child Alex, would you have what would you call it aborted me?
It's a fine. Oh, I'm so sorry. Oh my god
Well, I know his location
I know exactly what he looks like.
Well, I know his routine.
I'm not Russian.
I'm African American, but...
Only Russian.
Thank you, dude.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
You're back?
Okay.
Ghost is backstage too, but no ghost.
I don't want to talk to Gus. I want to talk to you.
Stop cutting the blacks to accept you, Alex. The blacks do not accept you.
I've talked to them. I have my black carrying card.
We talked. You're not black.
Okay, that's to my benefit.
Just let you know. Stop claiming blacks. Stop claiming African-American.
Your African-American rights have been revoked.
That's to my benefit. Continue.
That's very racist of you to say that.
Do you get out of speeding tickets now?
You do know I know where you live, right?
You said that a bunch of times, but you won't even
give me the proper location, which makes me feel that you're full of shit.
You're just upset that I have a better broadcasting voice than you do.
They said I'm too skinny myself.
No you don't.
100% you do.
You know about your nieces and nephews.
I've tried being nice to you and you're still a guy.
So you know I know about your nieces and nephews, correct?
Like this shit does work on wine. Wine moms. That's a quite a working old Steve
So, you know, I know everything about you really
You if I want even since listening Alex the audience is listening
Give a little teaser
There's I have the better radio voice than you do. I admit that I have the better radio voice than you
See you Pokemon wins. They're all pretty good. Yeah, admit it. I know
Flirting are you flirting with me Alex stop?
I'm not my family I can tell you that because I've watched your pornography. I found it boring
Why would you watch my pornography unless you're Alex you're a crazy person on the internet?
Why wouldn't I watch your pornography?
She totally wants to fuck me
Well, okay, it's a word of
See Pokemon show every day
Works on the wine bombs it does that work every single thing
Do you really make a mood including the size of my way, huh? Oh sweetie kiss kiss
That's about what four inches. Yeah
He's got, she's, R.G. was on her,
I'm not a fan of what I'm talking about.
Parents.
R.G.
I lost his ear face.
You're not attractive.
I'm adorable.
I've had many, many people.
I'll tell you what this guy actually looks like.
What's that?
He looks like
If Steven Seagal were to have been punched in the face and nobody were to have repaired the
procedure.
You just couldn't afford a surgery to fix it.
Pretty good.
I'll take that.
That's a good look like.
Yeah, I know everything about you.
That was a good line.
I'm adorable.
Absolutely adorable, Alex.
That's the thing.
I'm adorable.
You're disgusting, and you're short.
That's what's funny.
I've been told I look exactly like my dog
if I'm being quite honest with you.
How can you go like a dog disgusting?
A dog would be better looking than you.
Look at that, that's a beautiful dog.
Yeah, exactly.
I thought you'd be better looking.
I'm not a canine person, not with me at all.
You're not a animal person in general, are you?
Yeah, you're into the worst kind of stuff.
You don't really like animals, do you?
Pleasant.
You're not the way that you're unlovable.
You're not capable of giving or receiving love.
You've proven this over and over again through what your entire life
100% I've been
Amazingly not
But you are somebody who's a very
Eightfold individual who basically I've been nothing to miss you. I've only called you a cunt once there's somebody who never should have been born
You're somebody who, aesthetically, is not very attractive.
Your point is disgusting.
You're somebody who has to go all the internet without showing their face because you're not good enough to help.
No, I don't show my face because of crazy people like you.
Because you're a loser because you're an ass.
I don't show my face because of crazy people like you.
seen somebody who never should have been born. That is your reality. You pathetic little
piece of shit. If I ever to kick your ass in the face, I would do it without.
But no matter what, it doesn't have to do with race.
It doesn't have to do with clack.
It doesn't have to do with anything.
You're drunk on the phone.
You're a literal piece of garbage.
It's the nicest thing you've ever said to me.
Who never said a thing to a boy.
That really is.
And the sooner that you can put a goddamn gun to your head.
I thought you were supposed to put a gun in my head.
Finally be happy
It's like something I've never heard before
I just want to put a gun to your own
right between the eyes.
You said you've done it before.
You make me sick.
I've already seen what you look like.
You said that, Goomba's time.
You're approved for that.
You have very strange eyes to be honest with you, and then that makes me wonder what's your mother rate?
I think she was.
She was. I think your mother was right by you.
It was true, brother.
Shining through.
Yeah.
Your mother was a rape victim.
It's crazy.
And that is why you come on the internet.
It's so weird.
They
Look at you you hear my radio voice
There was a rape victim all spring.
My broadcasting, boys, is making you try to stimulate your clip
by moving like that.
You can't fool me, woman.
Well, this is also R.D. dog.
He assumes we're rape gang victim.
That is who you are.
The rape gang victim.
That's why you call yourself a dog.
Maybe it's just rape.
You're unlovable.
Alex, that's what these cigarettes do, right?
I can do that, let's go with it, there it is.
A rape offspring, a rape gang offspring, that is you.
You're just a horrible person.
Inside of that, I love it.
You are a rape gang offspring.
I was being nice to her too, this is where we're at.
Rapist men, rapist dogs. I mean, can I have a shake's curtain off?
Your mom wants you to rapist.
Yes, that is the reality of the army.
Oh, oh, oh, I don't know what it would be.
True colors shine through, we can see your true colors, that's why we love you.
He's a werewolf, he's a teen wolf I guess. Teen wolf, some sort of a...
Maybe he's like...
Of a canine offspring, well that's how we got the, what do they call them, big...
Werewolves?
That's what they are. He's a big foot. Everyone will wonder about it, but that's what he is.
It's because of the rape gang. Because of the rape gang. I owe my life to that rape gang.
You have to wake up every morning and be like, all you have to do is consult the people
over at Guy in TV.
Okay.
This is a happy shower, Alex.
We do know you have the autism.
Not too great with the personal hygiene.
Got you kicked out of porn industry.
We know that.
That doesn't even make any sense.
All of it sure would make complete sense.
I know you're a part of the rape game.
It's called Vagicill.
Vagicill.
Yeah, you're somehow
mentally deficient.
I mean, I'm such a woman
who is on so many
levels above you.
Above you.
Have I read your voice better than your radio
voice? Admitted.
I would ever
You're just mad that my radio voice is better than yours, that's why you're mad.
Yeah. Old fashioned weirdo from another time that never should. Oh, I thought it was a
rethink of where my mom was, rather. Well, your mom definitely should not have conceived you.
Yes. Well, I mean, thank God, you won't be ever conceived, right? Thank the Lord for that. Oh,
I've already been conceived, but you've never shown. No, you will not conceive,
meaning you will have any children to pass on your mental illness. Oh, I'm so sure.
You absolutely cannot, that's a lie, don't lie to the folks out there.
You absolutely cannot conceive, you cannot have children, your uterus is trying up, don't
lie to the people.
But the reason you can't is because you're undesirable.
I'm going to see what people want.
You are very distressing.
Your nose alone as...
And you pass as...
I have a very adorable nose.
No, I've seen you.
You pass as Caucasian, but your nose strangely...
It screams a tube.
No?
It's I think you're are you actually black passing us white? Is that what it is?
Got me folks. I do go by black rg
When I saw your picture
See this again
This is why I say
I had the black card Alex you could not claim black
It is no we do not accept you
Oh, well, he's admitting that he's a nigger. Good.
Okay. Excellent. His nose. I've never seen a nose as long as this person. His nose is literally like...
You're just trying to say you got a nigger nose.
Well, you are a nigger without doubt.
I finally got it, Jay.
I'm very happy.
I've never seen a face as ugly as yours.
I'm adorable.
It's the tenth time.
Blame me.
No, you're not adorable.
You're passing us one.
So adorable.
But you're very ugly.
um passing and I have a better broadcasting voice than you have.
No, you're a solid nigger.
You're always talking about how wonderful your voice is.
Mine is so much better.
I've never said that.
You're a solid nigger, yes.
Can you sing Endless Love for us?
Why would I do anything?
You're obviously in love with me.
Obviously.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You're just a solid, white trash nigger, that's you.
Do you think I couldn't sing true colors?
I certainly can't sing that.
So you're a solid, white trash nigger
of nigger, white trash nigger.
You're actually like an elementary kid.
Cut it out.
I'm telling you.
I'm not interested.
I've seen you fuck Alex.
Well, I don't know what you're looking at, but you're a solid white trash.
I'm looking at your porn, and I'm telling you, you cannot fuck.
I don't know what you're talking about, but you're a solid white trash nigger,
and your mother is a solid white trash nigger, as is your father, a solid white trash nigger.
You're a nigger sock, that's all you are.
It's amazing.
Don't repeat.
I know.
This is amazing.
Amazing, Alex.
You never, you never see who amaze me.
You always deliver the good.
Who never should have been conceived,
never should have been born.
It should have been exterminated, probably.
With the Jews, right?
With the rest of the Jews?
Exactly.
See, I'm glad we're on the same page.
Yes, we are.
Oh my god.
We are.
You know, we should, let's co-host the show together.
We can do this all together after this.
They were amazing guys.
Why would I want to just only talk to a white trash?
You had a broadcast-y voice.
I have a broadcast-y voice.
It should have been, like, ebony and ivory,
except you're the ivory and I'm the ebony.
And you know, I'm too good for you.
You should have been exterminated.
No, you're not though.
You're not though.
Yeah, it's not silly.
Who's joining us, Alex?
Come on, she has a history.
and burn your ass externally.
You can burn me every night if you want to.
Let's make a show.
Well, I'm already...
I've already...
You'll be my YouTube dream.
to do a show with a failed ex porn star.
I've already done it.
Who was ever going to do that?
Yeah, yeah, we were already done it.
I mean, the world loves autistic porn, sorry.
No one awards it to everyone talking about it.
The world loves ex-autistic porn, sorry.
You're a white-
You should have been put into the incinerators.
And you will, eventually.
Wow.
She always says that about people.
As you get that mischievous look on your face,
when you know you're saying that word,
and it makes me laugh every time.
Well, what are you going to do about it?
Nothing.
I'm nothing.
I think it's hilarious.
I'm sorry, why?
I'm not some white mom who's going to be like, oh.
She said she knows my location.
Well, I do.
No, you don't, though.
And you've never seen my face.
You're a horrid, awful woman.
I've definitely never seen it.
So she just sits here and judges other people.
I've seen this face.
Yeah, absolutely have not.
I'm giving you permission to show it, right?
Yeah, 100%.
I don't have any permission.
I'm giving you permission to post it
on your community while tonight.
This is foreplay, folks.
I've washed your pornography. I found it boring.
I get washed with porn too.
Good stuff talking about it, bitch.
Finish it.
Well, no, because it's a part of your life, right?
Yeah, you failed to mention that you got thrown out for hygiene reasons and you should own stock and that's the white nigger
Yeah, I love her so much. I really do. Let's do a show together Alex. Come on
Come on. Let's do a show together
It would be fun. Look you're smiling that you know, you this not the side that you had to stroke on on the face
But the other side
You know because you get you almost
Right half your face out of stroke. You could definitely
Everybody's reporting your friends show because of your ass. No, you're a horrible
Drawing an N word not me
No, but it's a key is my friend. Thank you
Nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger nigger stay classy Alex
Okay, nigger
Come on, let's do a show together, Alex.
Okay, yeah, so I ended it right then, you know,
because I cannot.
Hi, everybody.
Thank you for joining me for my live lesson today.
There it is, okay.
Hey, what's up guys?
So that was great, but I mean, there's something on Rumble.
I mean, I would always like stop playing this
because I was like talking about her
after we made up and stuff, but.
See now it's relevant and see that's a beautiful part about having a fight with her then you have all this old content
I can suddenly play again. I mean it's like
But the one on her too. She's she like has I mean she's but she's like way way more
She is like so many people she's done this with that. It's like we can give it to a science now
We're writing a book. We're teaching a class called like, you know, how to
Had a you know avoid Alexander Mayer. Okay, hold on one second. Tripp kick
This is so you'll see it. I don't know if you've heard of Osho. He's a spiritual. He's like a from from India and stuff
This video has been a few months ago because this was when we were fighting and it's pretty good
It's a I had one of one made of me where I'm Charles Manson, but this one is Osho and it's impressive here
It's called Wild Wild Psyche
Crazy stuff, huh? I don't think there's any. You know what?
Let's just begin. I've got tons and tons of it and I can find it all through uh, you know, oh show
Okay, yeah, so I'm oh show in this video. See here we go
Everybody felt they were there at the beginning of the great experiment
Like we were the chosen people.
But Guant's agenda was simply to raise the consciousness of humanity that was his goal.
America was land of promise.
It was my conviction we will have no problems.
I don't think America has a place for these people.
Everyone in Antelope mistrust Rajneesh.
I want that guru and his evil influence out of my city.
They're run by satanic power.
There is a talk of vigilantes who may seek revenge on the Rajneesh's.
A bomb went off in the middle of the community.
More than 60 followers evacuated.
It was a catastrophe.
Mostly unjust terrified.
If I didn't take measures to protect our community,
No one else would do it.
Somebody else made this. This guy made this.
Disarm this cult's army now.
If the government does decide to get you,
they're going to get you.
There is bias, there is prejudgment,
religious discrimination, and this is democracy.
I've had enough of it.
We are going to mount a full-scale assault.
We will be ready to protect ourselves.
I've grown up in the standing, thou shalt not kill me.
What had happened?
There's darkness in all of us.
Doesn't make you a bad person.
You know, Christine told her own son,
go jump off a bridge,
and then she said,
she did, but...
It's been to like an alligator-vested pond or something.
It's a very confusing story, I don't quite know.
It was a very confusing story.
First of all, why would she say that to her son?
Second of all, she said it.
Why would she then say don't?
I mean, but she did say jump off a bridge.
It's okay.
Christine, I said sacrifice babies in the woods.
You can tell me to jump off a bridge, okay?
But you know, then they're saying,
oh, I was so drunk as a scum.
Hey, first of all,
Really?
I don't really drink.
Beta. Beta.
You don't really drink?
Almost every time I hear you,
you're so fucking drunk as a skunk,
I can't even barely hear
your high-pitched Minnie Mouse voice.
How many wings have you built
on the White Claw Factory?
How many wings have they built?
How many...
Cars to the executives of white Claw own
Just based on your on your monthly consumption, and you're telling me I only he's drunk
I mean that was a little bit ridiculous and what why is it anybody saying anything to her? Oh
We'll be that you're uh, you're not only a drunk. You're a mean drunk. I mean, maybe I'm a sober
I'm not I'm kind of mean, but yeah
Oh shit
I mean, okay, the yelling in the supermarket, that was okay.
The bothering the lady at the Tempur-Pedic mattress store,
that was a little bit low.
I didn't like what he did at the fish counter either.
Asking for a poop fish, that's really inappropriate.
But then, he thinks it's his human right
to come on my panel, right?
He's like, oh my God, he wouldn't let me on his panel.
Yeah, first of all, you're not an interesting guest.
pompous and like, oh, I mean Tommy, what, what do you think you're, you know, what, you're not Tom
Cruz or I don't know Tommy Lee Jones or whatever. I don't know Tommy James. I think there's another
guy named Tommy James a singer or something like that. You're not him. I heard you rap with Alexandra.
It's terrible. Shameful. Even if that says anything about my music, you have to hear
the rain falls down their duet.
Okay, I don't want to pick on her but she's now she's posting more stuff. She posted
you know
What looks like an AI of me burning in a dumpster with what looks like an elderly woman and
You know Bill Cosby I think it might have been I think she was trying to do beta and salmon
But it didn't quite work, but it's okay. I looked pretty good, but you know what? I am on fire
I'm on fire, but you know what? I'm crawling out of that dumpster. You left me in
Alexandra. Hey, by the way, who wants to go to Alexander's Bible study? Is anybody?
Oh, no, no, we're, nobody wants to go. Don't you know she has great religious advice for
us all? And Bronzeberg too. These are just these wonderful people. I offended Jesus apparently.
He has, you know what you do? We'll go over there. She has it every day. Go listen to her
Oh wait, she doesn't do that. She doesn't preach for good.
I think she's more of an Old Testament soul.
God, pretty much just fucks everyone over.
Thank you, dude.
Oh, but apparently I'm Jewish.
Good times is Jewish.
Beda's Jewish.
Thank you, Mercury and Scorpio.
I know, but that's what Bronzeberg said.
Nobody's disagreed.
I didn't see anybody say,
Yeah, he's like, oh, that's offensive to Jesus.
Jesus is my homeboy. I would have said the n-word, but that would have been offensive
Yes, he did say that didn't he you heard it you heard it here first. What do you use it? Bronzeberg?
You're just that you're the you're the the conduit to Jesus
Someone said my my beard looks like a brillo pad in the picture
I thought hey, maybe I'll like look a little bit like fresher or something like that and I won't look like a
And where's that my bum that lives in a house
If I'm a bum, I'm a bum with the nicest fucking apartment in the world.
How do I look now?
Thank you so much.
I look warm?
Oh, thank you.
I am warm.
We're talking about, not talking about Big T's buttworms, are you?
That was such a disgusting story.
And you know what's more disgusting?
Tripp Kicks said he would still bang it.
Like, okay, Tripp Kicks.
No, Tripp Kicks.
Oh, sweetheart.
Tripp Kicks.
Oh, like, oh, yeah.
Okay.
I don't care. Get out of here, Tony. You're not welcome, you bitch. Die. Fuck.
I'm so fucking annoying. Die, Tony. Find another guy. All right. I'm straight now, didn't you hear?
Alexandra said so. And so it didn't beat it. Actually, we're all saying I'm straight now,
right? Okay, got it. Hold on. We're all saying I'm straight. I never thought I'd find the day
or like being straight would be the insult. Like, oh, he's straight. And they're like,
I don't need any more, these women.
I mean, I say I love women, but not to date.
I mean, I've been through enough.
What's against TOS?
What?
Out!
Who are these people?
It's all the same loser.
Where's your channel, Tony?
Oh, yeah.
It's all me.
His channel is all me.
Oh, oh, sweepy, like, comments on a lot of people.
I've never seen one beat a clip on sweepy's channel.
All I see is a bunch of me, and I thought Canada dry.
And I think he reported her stream.
Maybe he's the one that reported it.
It's not blaming me for everything.
My responsibility is to save your channel,
call me dirty, and-
Soccero.
Oh, I need to defend Sweet Pea and Tracy.
These women are vicious.
Do you hear what they said to this guy, Michael?
You should hear.
That's why they don't want me playing old clips.
They're revealed.
Those true personalities are revealed.
They're fakeness.
I'm going to continue to play their clips,
because it's not their clips, it's my clips.
Michael, my show, my property of my show.
I can play anything I want on my show.
They're so paid.
The people get obsessed.
It's usually-
I mean fucking-
Spider rituals.
It goes on a hundred accounts.
Go flush yourselves down the toilet, okay?
They had a spider ritual named after me.
Really?
Oh, he doesn't make content.
Wait, Tommy, that's what that was?
Will you speak falsely for God or speak directly before him the world? Yeah, I know isn't that mercury, right?
Isn't that so so why would wrong for me be doing that? I don't speak directly for him
I never said I was Jesus. I said I tried to be Christ like and that's joke too. I know all about you know
Sam what's the guy's name?
I've been taking digestive care for eight and a half years.
It's a wonderful product.
It has greatly improved my digestive system.
Semiazza, oh, shut up this day.
Oh, look, are you Tony?
This day was Tony the whole time.
Well, you're reported.
I hadn't hit all, I hadn't hit bits or 36 accounts.
I don't care if you report me.
I'm not doing anything wrong.
What did I do?
Did I say the N word?
Like you do all the time?
Yeah, shouldn't they?
They should be worried about themselves.
Like, why are they, why am I being lectured on religion
by Alexandra Mayers and Bronzeberg, you know?
And rather listen to, you know,
any nut on a street corner has more sense
than these two people do about religion.
What?
I am trying to be Christ-like.
You know what Christ says?
Forgive, love your neighbor, you know,
turn the other cheek.
He didn't say,
You know call everyone a human trafficker didn't say just dump your friend for no reason and then and then
Start start a fucking slandering them every second you get
It's true. They aren't qualified to speak the way none of us. No, but I think that we there are some people that yeah
There are some people that maybe not speak for God, but like, you know, they can they just give their
Yeah, it's like if they were actually like set the example and I maybe I'm not sending the perfect example either
But you know Jesus got mad too at some of the stuff that went on
He turned over some tables at the church and stuff like that these things were not fair
Forgive the other fifth stage. What is he gonna say reported because if you say you're gonna report my channel
It's not it's not a funny joke or anything. So you
Apologize you apologize to me
Beg me for forgiveness. Okay, then
I'll think about forgiving me.
I will forgive them, but I need to be asked for forgiveness.
Hi, Bayclips, how are you, sweetie?
I'm, oh my gosh, sweetie.
I know, I know she did the spider ritual.
It's okay.
I know witchcraft too, and I'll just all backfire on them.
It's like, what?
First of all, you're not supposed to kill spiders.
Oh my gosh, each account blocked is another report?
I care.
I survived Alexandra Mayer's and Bita.
Am I scared of you?
Am I still I don't have one strike on my account. I'm like so in the clear
What reported you think YouTube cares about you you make YouTube any any money even though I don't make the much money
Make them more than you. I promise you
Six age all you do is take up their bandwidth with your you know fraudulent accounts
Oh my god, he's on so many outs. Yeah, I have like 11 accounts, but do I use any of them? No
I used I used it, you know, I have a backup one backup channel. I don't go in anybody
I mean geez people are just just worried to come up with this
Oh shut the fuck up. Okay guys, can I get a mod helping me out with this? It's like a little bit too much
I just want I'm trying to get a thought out and it's like he just keeps coming with more accounts and stuff
He's a tech guy who cares
It's not really like rocket science.
You just have to be kind of nice to me.
Even if like, like he man skated through like for months,
almost a year, like skated through.
Okay, good.
Yeah, you're gone.
Bye.
This is no, oh my gosh.
Please, do you think I care?
You're Christine, right?
That's the only person that calls me scumbag is Christine.
That's her word.
You can't use it, okay?
It's like, I'm the only one allowed to talk about,
you know, sacrifices in the woods.
Christine is the only one allowed to say scumbag.
Okay.
Peek-a-boo.
Isn't this crazy?
I thought this stage was like a cool person.
No, he's not.
But Christina, oh, and also I'm not the baby of my,
oh, Christina's like, oh, he's probably just the,
he's a baby of his family, blah, blah, blah.
You know, I do have older brothers and sisters,
but I have younger brothers and sisters too.
I was a middle, I was a Jan Brady of my family.
I wasn't, I was coddled by nannies.
I never had a nanny.
We had, we had, you know,
Guatemalan housekeeper once in a while, but.
You know, I'm not never a nanny.
Fran Drescher came over.
You know who has a less annoying voice than Bita?
Fran Drescher.
Why am I being like, attacked for like, you know,
trying to have a say on for Michael and stuff, right?
Who is my friend.
And these people that call, like, to today,
today even they call them like a terrible things.
And it's like, I'm not allowed to say.
Michael, Tracy's not here, come here,
she's not gonna ask you for the money, right?
And it's like, I'm the piece of shit,
but they're calling him pieces of garbage
and all this kind of stuff.
And I mean, really, does it make sense?
Does it make sense to me?
Ah, stop.
It is cool, but six people left.
And so I'm gonna stop it.
I'm gonna stop it.
I know she does to everyone.
I know she does to everyone, but I'm not everyone.
Why does six people leave just there?
I don't understand.
Are people fucking retarded?
Really?
Ugh.
I'm glad they left, but fuck people.
Fuck people.
That's when you, oh, oh, he's playing AI songs.
If any of these people,
if any of these people ever use AI,
I'm gonna catch every single one of these motherfuckers
who has a problem with AI,
and I'm gonna catch them using it.
I call it Black RG using it.
Oh yeah, I saw the Groovy Jimin.
I saw that on Vitas when she had to restart her stream,
Black RG.
You have to keep calling me out on it right? I like you black RG. You don't have to keep saying
You get it
I'm not not denying that I do it. I mean jeez
To keep calling me out. Yes. We know I use it use it to make these two photos of groovy Jimmy
Now I'm gonna with the 30 people
Maybe you go fuck. Hey my chance going crazy
of psyche, psyche question real quick.
What do you do when your chat's going against you?
What do I do?
I start ignoring it and hope for a...
You ignore them?
Yeah, thank you, dude.
You got to go to bed.
Oh, thank you God, body for coming.
Yeah, yeah, thank you for coming.
Yeah.
But you know what I do, I pay attention.
You take a peek of my chat.
Leon, look what they're saying.
Take a peek.
You're saying terrible things about you?
Yeah, they're, they're hating on my motion.
Tell them you're Mexican in your protected class, and if you're they'll
They're, they're hating because I have relationships with like yours and everything.
What do you mean like, like mine?
Like, they're like, why, why do you, why, why do you not hate psyche?
I'm like, why would I hate them for?
Hey, I'm sorry. I'm gonna turn against you. Yeah against anybody else
I mean, it's like and a lot of people is that why is that a thing?
Why is that a thing because I
I'm stupid and I let this guy named Brandon like, you know
Who's very controversial people said don't have them on and then I throw everyone fuck off and I'll have it
Whatever I want on so I had them on haters. They're haters, but then he turned on me and now he's like trying to like look in
Docs me saying I have AIDS and and pretending he's like a 12-year-old girl
pretending to be trying to be my mod in the chat and stuff like that.
That means he's delusional then.
Yeah, we know he is.
He's delusional.
Delusional.
Not dilusional.
Yeah, not dilusional.
He's delusional.
But uh, he's like the Mariah Carey song.
You've been losing your mind.
Are you getting out?
Are you not people that type in your chat?
You just convinced his retards that are stupid.
Well, you know what it's like I don't care if there's like not a lot of people like usually if there's a lot of people typing
Half of it is bullshit and stuff
I like if I like if there's a few people and they're just typing good things and like we're having a chat and like laughing
Yeah, that's all I want. That's what it's about. Yeah, I don't care how many people there
I've had a hundred people that there's nobody buying readings or become a member or buying a website thing
but or if you say bad things but don't be like a
Like a vein praying for bad
I don't know drama is like really easy to get to get a burnt out on and I like to but then it's good people complain when I try
I wouldn't do anything except like there's have people fighting on the panel
like I just I have I try to like do cool songs and music and different like you know art and
I put a lot of creativity and then they're like, oh, well you use AI
I mean you understand AI is like it's gonna be like the key to the future
I mean it's like really though. It's like it takes any kind of if you have a talent
It can expand upon that talent like it does because you figure out what you're good at
and when you're not good at, it can help you compensate and so it does the work that you can do.
Like for example, if I do a song, I don't know how to play many instruments or not very good.
Yeah, but some people are delusional on their own talent.
Right. Oh, they think they're so talented, right?
No, they feel like they're not that talented, but they really do have that talent.
Well, everybody has some intelligence.
Like, there's some kind of intelligence, or like, there's some kind of...
Why does he have to take an intelligence to show your talent?
Because talent is part of intelligence.
Like, a talent...
Yeah, look at porno girls.
Yeah, that's what a talent is.
Is that a talent?
Is taking ten digits of talent?
What's their worst talent they're showing?
double anal.
They're putting their pussy and their legs and their asses.
Well that's talented.
I mean it's like, it's like, it's like an acrobatical, I guess.
It's like Cirque du Soleil.
What if somebody knows how to really do something, magic trick or something?
I know a magic trick.
Oh boy.
That's why I keep wanting to meet you because I can show you my magic trick.
Hey, I can hit it once, I can hit it.
Oh, that's the 57th song.
My girl got talents.
You do?
No, it'll suck the nigga out in 1.5 seconds.
Oh my God, I love that.
Monday, I love it rough.
Thank you.
Thank you, Saiki.
Yeah.
He's like, not me though, not for real though, he's like, you be like, not me.
If you went out with your wife and I, or your girlfriend or wife, yeah, or wife.
My ex, psyche, we went out together, my girl gets it on altercation, we're gonna have her
back though.
Yeah, but while you have to fight, I'm gonna also do it with the, I'm gonna get kind of
stupid.
She's gonna do the fighting.
Oh, she will?
Okay, good.
I mean, it's amazed like the IP2 people.
She's gonna do the fighting and we're gonna be the ones like.
Yeah
The ring girls were like we're gonna be like on the side of the ring like with
Cheerleaders and stuff. I don't want to get I don't want to fight people
Right you see like the girls fighting there's a girl's fight
We're scary they're like
And they're like pointy says hair basses and they're gonna say, let's say we're all hanging out together
And there's someone like freshie
Then I'm gonna say I say through mrs. Glow get up get up and do your thing
Go punch them in the face
Yeah, you I mean it's like I love when women handle things because because they can they just like you know
Men like to do things and some women let men do things sometimes. Oh women can actually do everything
They can I had 11 viewers constantly now
Good you have more than me now. I mean you're in now
Yeah. Well, I mean, everyone's left in my show, but you know what?
I had seven likes, no dislikes in my video, in my livestream.
Well every stream I get like so many dislikes that I bear basically have like zero people zero likes ever because
Sexy and cool
That I'm real that means that YouTube's gonna might be hiring soon. Oh, yeah, like rumble or YouTube or a kick
I'm all rumble and they like me. I
Want to rumble are you ready to rumble?
What you're trying to do is I just want to wrestle with you. I'm gonna call off tomorrow. Let's hang out. Okay. I
Mean I'll out tomorrow. You don't know hang out and drink a beer. I'll drink a beer
But that yeah, pretty much I have enough
Stream it let's stream it and drink a beer and then we cut off streaming. I'm totally down with it
It was Tuesday. Yeah, you're down. Yeah for sure
Let's make it like a movie let's hang out
Here I'll actually give you my phone number
Just just just hit me up on my Instagram
Okay, I forgot. Oh you remember Instagram. I have to go back and look at my messages and stuff. When did you hit me up?
I hit you up by Instagram, I got you on Instagram.
Man, months, or like a long time ago or what?
Like two days ago, I got your Instagram.
You're all looking at your ass.
I did?
Oh my God, that was you?
Oh, thank you.
That was me.
Hey, do you want to see my friend?
That was just in the chat and he went to bed,
but do you want to see what he does?
Why not?
He wants to be.
I don't know what he looks like, okay?
Hold on a second.
So here's his name is Godbody and...
He's my friend. I found him one day. I was like, wow, this guy's hot and
He came to my chat tonight. He's really fun. Okay, so here he is and but this is how he appeared when he started
He this is a little
It's psyche awakens. Oh
Yeah, so here's God body guys. It's PH
PSY CHE
AWAKENS
Oh, yeah, you show me your dick.
I did not.
Look at this guy.
They're all saying your messes.
Hey, what the fuck is wrong with that dude?
The guy that was just my chef.
That dude's going through something.
He, like, does, like, push-ups with, like, an axe on her.
That's the guy that was just my chef.
That's the guy that I...
That's a lot of free time.
I like to push him.
With the strong core at home, he's in an axe.
Underhand grip on the body, overhand grip next to the blade, legs shoulder width, and just going to swing this way, swing that way, this way, that way.
I think I'm in love!
I know a lot of people that don't even try to be a war activist or what you're going to do is
He's not wrong. He's not wrong. Yeah, he's not wrong. I'm tightening up. There should be man around this world now in 2020 and 2026. Yeah, man, my credit card.
Hey, the world is like fucking so fake. I mean, all this alien is
It's called that's what's called VR like virtual reality is like we live in a virtual reality because everything's fake though
We're looking at everything. You know fake now all the screen everything that comes to the screen is
It's real psyche is fake
Either you gave for your own gayness or you gave for this gayness
right and it's like yeah and the game is doesn't even match the real gayness yeah it's not even
it can be so gay without even taking a talk ever because you're gay yeah they're straight guys
real gay niggas they they the song you gayness who made this song the gayness well no they're not
the what do you mean the real gay niggas like you're talking about they uh they ain't real what oh come
Don't think I want to this is real but the realness ain't gay
Hey, bitch, bitch, bitch is niggas and niggas
I'm younger than you okay, hold on watching what you're saying
You're playing out like I'm like damn this is really gay these fools are gay. I'm gay. I'm not straight. Everyone keeps saying I'm straight
I know I'm not, is what I'm saying.
Everyone's saying I am, like Alexander's saying,
oh, he's straight, you know, I got it,
it's massive.
Because you get girls in your channel,
you get girls.
I don't know, I'm beautiful women,
I don't know, I just think I love beautiful women,
but you know, but the problems are all crazy.
Titties in his channel and his stream.
Yeah.
Everybody's like, aren't you gay?
Yeah, exactly. They want to show to your channels like you're on live, right?
And now they're like, oh my god. Oh, he had a predator on the show. I mean, it's like
What's her name the black girl she really fucks with you
She doesn't turn on me now. She's doxing me today. My family is terrible. Oh
She turned on me for no reason. She went crazy. She's like fuck. Yeah, cuz you're gay
Yeah, I mean she wanted my baby at one point now. She says I'm like, you know the seed of Satan
I mean she was being gay too. She is. I mean she wants to be a gay white man
She said I'm thinking she just wanted to take over my body
Exposed that I'm exposing it. I did tonight
Hey, I have I have it all. Did you see my skin on these people judge you? I don't those motherfuckers
I know you're a real Nick. I've all listen. I've right. I've been I've had the best trap house in Los Angeles
And this is a big city. Hey to live in Cali. I know you're a main head
If you never live in California by the beach or done some drugs by the beach
You don't know shit, nobody knows you, nobody cares.
Right.
I mean, it's like, that's the thing too.
Like nobody knows me, but it's like,
and I have enough like shit about me
that people can talk about,
but they just make up shit though.
It's like, they're not telling me to do it.
Why do they make up shit on you, psych, you know?
Cause they're like, you're a lovable person.
That's fine.
I don't know. I mean, I think there's a jealousy involved.
I think there's a black magic or something involved,
maybe some too, but I kind of have to fight so much of it,
like so much evil eye and stuff.
It's just your vibe, fool.
Well, let's say, hey, hey, here, it's here.
Here, shake your hand with a black person.
Oh, shake your hand with Psyche.
That thing is so nice. You see, there's a difference.
Yeah, I mean they'll shake them in the black person but they'll say, oh, I don't like psyche because I
Yeah, they just don't like me so I want to show you I don't know if you ever saw the crystal Marie came on my show
Last year and this was that started all the trouble with Christine
That's how California is. This is these people come from everybody else, right psyche you got yours from
who the fuck knows
Yeah, it's crazy you're you're from cali we're from real cali south central cali we know how this
Hell yeah, we are
Yeah, oh my god, the meth has drug addicts. Well, you know, I like what is it called a land of broken dreams or something like that?
We have viewers that come over here and believe they have could change it. That's just not gonna change
No, very progressive state, but it's like yeah, no one no outsiders are gonna change
I mean it's like but there are the most beautiful people that come to here
Nobody nobody wants to talk about how the US is getting worse right now
Well fuck, I mean it's like you know because we want to stay positive. I mean, but it's like yeah
How much you think you're gonna pay for a hot cheeto by the end of the year?
I don't like I mean I
Usually
Pay for a coffee by the end of the year. I get free coffee is like seven dollars already. I get free coffee
So yeah, I buy it once for nine cents. Thank you. You're better than me
I can't wait to hang out with you and then share a squeeze orange juice for my girl
I thought you're I think it's a squeeze of your booty. I'm really the plan. You just said that
I'm not gonna touch you I promise
I'm not worried about the other bring her maize. You know if I don't worry about that
It is your girlfriend you worry about that cuz you're gonna touch me unless I let you cheese
Exactly, but you heard you heard of the Chicanas that like for the late break
Me know what somebody used to call me pay day. Oh, I know you're not like that, bro
I don't know who the fuck was telling you you're like that. I know you're not like that
I mean, I can play dumb.
I can play.
I am a fool.
No, I'm not beaters or not nothing, y'all.
I know you're not like that.
Yeah.
I mean, it's like, they just make shit up.
Because you live out there, you got to be.
You got to have some brain in your head.
I know redondo beats.
I know you got to have respect, because you'll get exposed.
Oh, yeah. I mean, I've been exposed. I mean, I didn't do anything and so I'm fine.
I'm just like, I mean, they can expose themselves. You know, it's like, that's all they do when
it's happening.
No, Trish, we're going to make something happen and then we're going to get the viewers going
crazy.
Okay, if we know what we would love it if we and 300 glow I have a collab if we like
We took donations to like to like
It's like you don't have a jacuzzi stream. Yes
Really might mind
Yeah, we can go into like one of the hotels and break in
All the good jacuzzi's are there they do my god. Yeah, I love I'll do jacuzzi
And I was wearing my American flag speedo. I was wearing them the other day because it's July
So I've been having sex with my girl for like two hours straight. You're gonna have to watch
I'm gonna watch
I'm gonna watch and just jerk off of my speedo unless I let you join but
Well, I promise I'll be I promise I'll be very good. You don't have to see yeah, I'll be behind you
You psyche you're gonna have to like you have to warm it up. Okay
Ah, there's a lot of pressure because you know, maybe I'm not maybe don't be as hot
I'm talking about having fun and getting I know I want to have fun
But I also maybe want a friend to kiss you once
Maybe if you let me hold you see my room. We're gonna have to wear lip gloss. Okay. I'm gonna get some berry flavored
Yeah, I want to have to put a barrier before that. Okay. No, I'm I was your teeth look fucked up for beer
Hold on one second. I'm gonna show my teeth. Let your teeth look yellow
Are they bad yeah, it's like it. We're not the work on that working out. Yeah
Hell no
This is green green. Come on. Look at your tongue. That should look like you got mushrooms coming off of it
I've brushed my tongue stop it
Hey Apollo, men are gay women are gay. USA is a friend of the gays. Sometimes it's like it is but it's like
So is Germany in the in the 20s
She got mushroom it does not
Well, do you like their magic mushrooms will hallucinate? Hey, no, but okay
So USA is like not it's like, you know in Germany in 1920s
They had a gay renaissance and it was like they had drag queens a cabarets gay clubs
They people they ignored the laws about it
Then the Nazis came in and put the gays in the camps and the gays were like three worse than anyone else
Well, I was just explaining to him. I mean geez, okay, I've been looking for this crystal Christine clip
I mean, I don't know why it's so hard to find right now, but I played it the other day
It's so good. Okay, you're a you're a dick three in a glow, but I'll write you
I'm still looking for it though. So I need to go to the codex and figure it out. Okay crystal
Keep typing crystal cyclist crystal Christine. Oh here. Oh
Okay crystal
Drama unfolds a battle of crystal and Christine. I think this is it. Okay. Let me see if I can find this one. Okay
Drama unfolds. I'm gonna remember that title
Got it. Okay
Drama unfolds
The fuck the fuck? Maybe it was on the other channel. Hey, um, I can get the URL copy link
Okay, put the URL there. It's not in the paste. It's not there. Hmm. Let me look at it over here
So the video is private. Okay, so why is it on this channel?
It's a call. Oh my god. Okay, I'm gonna put on a video real quick here right back. Hi Paul. I love you
Thank you for being here. Appreciate you
We're back.
okay well anyway we're gonna get to uh some more of uh shaking my head productions
because i'm enjoying this disclosure stuff how bony baloney it is
Maybe that's why Alice got mad at me because I don't believe in aliens, really.
I mean, I believe they exist, I just don't believe that they're working with Steven Spielberg to
introduce themselves, you know, in the air and stuff, but let's see what happens.
Maybe I'm wrong. I just don't think so.
Okay, what is going on here? What is going on?
Kick off the Armageddon is coming soon. So Friday the 13th their black Friday coming up crack the codes is three months ago
Okay, March art of war. Okay. Here. You're in the right place. You know bad bunnies a
Big okay. No, okay
Iran's us ring in the antichrist
Times Square, I think it's the wrong channel. Hold on. Okay. Here we go
Okay, so
There is something about
Dark night 7-eleven, you know, there's a dark end of the soul too
But let's see what
My transformers walking around with us. It's just
Transformers
All right. Yeah, that is
Clowns in the world stage
Ronald McDonald house
You wanna see the Ronald McDonald one?
Looking for the disclosure. Where's the disclosure? I saw it. Yeah, I saw something to disclosure
If you believe we put a man on the moon, okay
Okay, I'm looking for where it says
something about
Disclosure
I saw something but okay
You're calling like the transgenders fought the fall and he's I don't know about that. It's kind of like a
They are kind of like an angel in a certain way, but I
Went too far down. Okay. Oh, here we go. This is pretty good. We give this a try
Get ready to follow. We're still here. Let me just mention briefly one thread in particular that should concern all Americans
Democrats Republicans and independents alike, especially those who serve in our Congress
the epidemic of malicious fake news and false propaganda that
flooded social media over the past year
It's now clear that
So-called fake news can have real-world consequences.
The U.S. Supreme Court has dealt yet another blow to the transgender community,
upholding state laws that bar transgender athletes from playing on women's and girls' sports teams.
By withholding...
you know, participation for transgender athletes in states that are enacting these
bans and by the Supreme Court affirming those bans, we're risking taking away a possible family,
a community, a sense of acceptance and belonging that would otherwise be found for these trans
athletes. What? Coach. Yeah. You what now? I understand why this is wrong. I mean,
But I am a woman.
I mean, all those years playing basketball, I never really felt like myself, a decade
in Hollywood trying to figure out who I really was and then I started working at the dollhouse
and this is the real me coach.
This isn't about politics or partisanship.
Lives are at risk.
Lives of ordinary people just trying to go about their days to do their jobs, contribute
It's a danger that must be addressed and addressed quickly.
Bipartisan legislation is making its way through Congress to boost the government's response
to foreign propaganda, and Silicon Valley is starting to grapple with the challenge
and threat of fake news.
Lena Haga is a 15-year-old trans athlete who runs high school track in Pasadena.
Haga says this ruling is definitely a setback, but not the end of the conversation.
The Supreme Court can't, you know, negate my truth.
I know who I am, and that's not something that they can ever take away from me.
It's imperative that leaders in both the private sector and the public sector step up.
to protect our democracy and innocent lives.
This country is founded by people who were in the aliens, man.
George Washington, man, he was in a cult.
And the cult was in the aliens, man.
You didn't know that?
This is Cara Danvers with Catco Media,
and this is a worldwide exclusive.
I'm here with a hero who has been fighting in the shadows.
This is Dreamer, my first question.
Who are you?
And I am a descendant of a daughter of Naltor.
When did you come here from Naltor?
I didn't.
I was born here in America.
I grew up in an idyllic town where humans and aliens
lived together in harmony.
The Supreme Court has struck down
President Trump's attempt to withhold American citizenship
from babies born to people in the United States temporarily
or illegally.
Trump's executive order on birthright citizenship
had always been considered to be something
of a legal long shot.
Ultimately, five justices found it unconstitutional.
Chief Justice John Roberts and Justices Sotomayor
Kagan, Barrett, and Jackson.
A sixth, Brett Kavanaugh, said it isn't permitted under federal law, specifically the Immigration
and Nationality Act.
Trump had talked about ending automatic birthright citizenship, going all the way back to 2015,
and signing this executive order was one of the first things he did in his second term
of office.
But, he repeatedly said he expected the court to rule against him.
You'll have 25% of the people coming into our country coming in through birthright citizenship,
and we won't have any control.
My mother was notorious, but my father was a human.
So you are both human and alien?
Yes.
My parents believed that humans and aliens could coexist,
and I am living proof of that.
But growing up wasn't easy.
I am also a trans woman.
I'm different, Ms. Danvers, but so is everybody.
And I don't know when that became such a bad thing.
We must commit ourselves to unconditional victory against them!
There's lots of buzz over Rudy Giuliani's impassioned speech at the Republican National Convention.
There's no black America! There's no white America! There is just America!
Now look what we've uncovered it's Giuliani showing his softer side dressed in drag in a comedy skit with Donald Trump
So I will continue fighting. I will continue fighting for acceptance and inclusion in the sixth three vote
The Supreme Court found the bans in Idaho and West Virginia don't violate the Constitution or Title IX the law that prohibits sex
discrimination in education
But the ruling likely extends to more than two dozen other states that have similar bans in place.
Girls do deserve to have fair and safe sports. It just puts us in the right direction to keep the fight going and to push even harder.
Sophia Laurie with the California Family Council says this adds fuel to the fire to put similar bans into effect in more than 20 other states.
including california jamal jeffreys is suspended indefinitely when he was thrown out of basketball
he was left with only one option i'm here no one's gonna leave him alone you did and now
with a new look a new team and a new problem oh my god lord what are you doing taking a shower
it's a whole new ball game look at you i got it a victoria secret where the secrets
The greatest gift we can give each other is our authentic selves and sharing that.
Sharing our truth is what will make us strong.
So here I am.
I am both human and alien, and I am the trans woman.
Supergirl, all new episodes Sunday at 8-7 central on The CW.
We're going to keep fighting because these girls deserve so much better.
California girls deserve to be protected.
And so we're going to continue to push on CIF.
We're going to try to introduce some more girls' sports bills.
We're trying to get CIF to follow Title IX
and ultimately just restore girls' rights.
Hey, my little monsters.
Are you having a good time?
Me too.
I was thinking before about my favorite festival experience,
because I know exactly how you all feel.
Ladies, today we're going to go over the guidelines
for a graceful, ladylike entree into society.
Make sure she's in the back with group photo.
Viola was facing a fate worse than death.
Ta-da!
Sorry mom, I have a strict no ruffles policy.
Until her twin brother Sebastian.
Where are you going?
London for a couple of weeks.
What are you going to do about school?
I was kind of hoping you could help me with that.
Showed her a way out.
Could you just like pretend to be me?
You don't want me to.
turn you into your brother?
Nobody in Lyria has even met Sebastian.
They wouldn't know the difference.
Now, she's headed to Illyria Academy.
Let's go, kick, kill!
Where the men have gained,
and the women have attitude.
Hey there, pretty lady.
Ew, girls with butts like mine
do not talk to boys with faces like yours.
Oh.
Everybody should try drag at least once.
It's really fun.
Even kids?
Yeah, there's actually quite a few kids
that are starting to do drag.
A drag queen is a character you create to express your feminine side or any other side
of yourself that you'd like to explore.
I'd like to be a superhero.
Yeah, you could be a drag queen superhero.
Yeah.
Who wants to be a drag queen when they grow up?
The Me Too movement against sexual harassment.
Is this the best a man can get?
Is it?
We can't hide from it.
Sexual harassment is taking over.
It's been going on far too long.
We can't laugh it off.
What I actually think she's trying to say.
Making the same old excuses.
Boys will be boys.
But something finally changed.
Allegation, assault, and sexual harassment.
And there will be no going back because we, we believe in the best in men.
Men need to hold other men accountable.
Well, sweetie, come on.
To say the right thing.
To act the right way.
Bro, not cool, not cool.
Some already are.
And ways big.
Y'all men, forever and ever.
And small.
I am strong.
Is not enough
Because the boys watching today
Chris Hemsworth
You know, you're really beautiful.
I'll go backstage before a show,
and I'm allowed to go in because I'm the owner of the pageant,
and therefore I'm inspecting it.
I've never seen him one time act inappropriate.
I just start kissing them, it's like a magnet.
And when you're a star, they let you do it.
You can do anything, whatever you want.
I can do anything.
I've never seen him one time.
One time.
Act inappropriate.
This may be the best of all.
Don't carry that, you're so, what are you, crazy?
Kids, name more pop.
Bruce Jenner all over the news,
the slow metamorphosis into this androgynous character he plays on TV, you know, the world's a stage.
No, your eyes don't deceive you.
That's Taylor Swift hugging Kylie Jenner, you know, the little sister of Kim Kardashian,
who at one point was enemy number one for the pop star.
You never know what it's going to be.
What up?
We're gonna be tight, bro!
Seriously, how old are you?
Uh, skip the couple grades.
There is something odd about that new boy.
Boom!
You are so much st-
But at this school, everyone's got a secret.
Duke wants Olivia.
Do you like...
Cheese?
Who wants Sebastian?
Isn't he cute?
How you doin', babe?
who is really Viola, whose brother is dating Monique.
So she hates Olivia, who's dating Duke, to make Sebastian jealous.
What does your heart tell you?
Huh?
I mean, which one would you rather see naked?
He is really Viola getting jealous, because she wants Duke, who thinks she's a guy.
Okay, okay, um.
And this is where it gets really complicated.
Excuse me, doofus.
sexual tension, male-female dynamics, all part of the high school experience.
That was pain.
I hate high school.
Is it just me or does this soccer game have more nudity than most?
This spring, I'm not really good at talking to girls.
Why? You're hot.
What?
You know, you're an appealing guy.
The secret is out. Amanda Bynes, Alex Breckenridge, Channing Tatum, Robert Hoffman, Vinnie Jones,
Laura Ramsey, and David Cross. I got baby trouble, sir. I got a left time of knowledge. She's the man.
Oh, right. Right now, you're covered in mud, and you're sweaty, and you smell, but you know why it's
Because what these festivals are all about is suffering for your love of music and I remember that my
Are you okay? I'm fine. It just threw up in my mouth a little bit
Snake alley is still there. I hope just fine. Thank you. We have about three questions for you
Indeed, we'll do the honors with question number one
It must be a great thrill to have a hit record. How do you feel about it?
Very good. First I really didn't know how to feel, you know?
Because this was really what all entertainers want, you know, you strive throughout for it.
And then you have so many ups and downs and you pay so many dues and when it finally gets there...
I don't guess you really know how to feel at first, and then it starts to settle down
and then it really soaks in, and I'm very proud and very happy.
Question number two.
Al, out of all the records you have recorded, how can you choose this one?
Well, the Brown Junior wrote the tune about approximately seven or eight years ago, and
he recorded it, and the only exposure it got was in the jazz world.
And I've always liked the tune, ever since I first heard it, which was about five years
And when Johnny Rivers presented the idea to me, you know, for it, because I really did like the tune and I liked the story behind it and everything, and there was no problem.
Okay, last question.
If your singing career was ever to be ended, what would you choose to go into?
Well, for the last class until here, I will sing around the world. I think I'll start playing drums.
All right. Al Wilson, thank you very much. I hope you can come and visit with us one of these days soon. It was nice talking to you.
R.L. Wilson and the Snake.
This decision by the Supreme Court is a very big one.
They'll probably rule against me because they seem to like doing that.
Here's what this decision turned on.
For five justices, it came down to the 14th Amendment of the U.S. Constitution, ratified in 1868.
That amendment opens with the Citizenship Clause.
All persons born or naturalized in the United States and subject to the jurisdiction thereof are citizens of the United States.
Oh man, they were weighing in that type of stuff.
from there man it was the last day of school uh Mr. Crawford I was thinking that maybe you and I
could get together over the summer I mean they don't be legal. It was the first day of summer
vacation. Do you guys know anything about a party here tonight? No sir.
It was a time they will never forget.
There's no fast in the making as we speak.
I thought he was cute.
Alex, this guy was cute then.
Do you remember when he graduated?
We were like three years old.
Hunter Biden, the son of US President Joe Biden,
is facing a possible jail term after being convicted
for gun crimes.
Let's go live to US correspondent Miley Hogan.
Miley, a jury found him guilty on all three counts.
Chevron that good morning they did and it was a quick decision as well
They only deliberated for three hours across two days to come back with this verdict
Finding that the US president's son Hunter Biden it was guilty on all three counts of
Chargers relating to possession of a weapon
While using narcotics now it was found that Hunter Biden lied on the federal forms or the background check of sorts saying that he was not
Using drugs or addicted to drugs at the time of purchasing that weapon now during this trial
Hunter Biden's addiction to crack cocaine was really laid out but it's not a
subject that Hunter Biden has shied away from publicly before. You asked me you
asked me a question back in May and you can repeat that question. The question we
answered back in May? You asked me a couple questions and what were those
questions? Do you smoke crack cocaine? Exactly. Yes I have some look to crack cocaine.
But no, do I? Am I an addict? No.
Do I have to be on camera?
For Titan's sake, just say something.
Uh, I am honored to work with Emperor Bellos in preparation for the day of Unibi.
I mean, Unili, I mean, uh, oh no, this is going all wrong.
Get me out!
Just cut the feed.
Now, Jackie, let's see your gymnastics routine.
Oh, tumbling.
Cute.
She spins 360 degrees!
Eh, not my best.
Next up, we have Lola performing...
Oh, uh, uh, ribbon dance.
Cute.
Up next, you know them as the manager of our local Creek Day King.
They watch your annoying siblings so you don't have to!
Give it up for A!
Hey, Angel. Good luck.
I didn't come here to make friends, Craig.
My esteemed judges, I brought for you today
Is this why you were swimming around our raft?
Were you looking for this?
The shoe must have floated away when they've shoved their limb legs.
Sorry we scared you.
How fascinating.
You've been putting salt water in-
This is cold stream and ice gator.
They prefer they than pronouns.
Being this bold in my presence.
Pretty cool trick, huh?
Lord Hordak, I'd like to introduce you to Double Trouble.
There are newest asset in taking down the rebellion when have I tried it?
Probably in one of my drunken stupors probably approximately about a year ago
Finally, I have to mention a man who's made life of the White House very sweet
This is one of Michelle and my favorite people are executive pastry chef Bill
Yosas who's here tonight
So he's this is the problem
We call Bill the Crustmaster because his pies, I don't know what he does.
Whether he puts crack in them or...
But...
You guys have got to try the cold choc.
I've got to try.
The White House is fighting back today against reports that the Biden administration is giving
away free crackpipes, saying the administration is instead sending money to communities across
the country to confront an overdose epidemic.
HACA United Washington correspondent Rashad Hudson gives us the details.
The Biden administration says it is not preparing to give out free crack pipes.
What we're really talking about here is steps that we're taking as a federal government to address the opioid epidemic.
The surprising rumor came after the Department of Health and Human Services discussed plans
for safe smoking kits. They say the kits are part of a $30 million harm reduction program
and don't contain pipes.
We're never a part of the kit. It was inaccurate reporting.
But Republican lawmakers like South Dakota Senator John Thune and Kansas Senator Roger
Marshall aren't convinced.
Well, I got the Pfizer and I would have been very happy with any of them
You know, you're really beautiful the spoof was filmed 16 years ago when Giuliani was mayor of New York for a charity dinner
So it was all in good fun. Oh, you tricky boy
Apologies for being rude. I was getting into character. Did it work be honest as always. I'm open to constructive criticism
action. Welcome to meditation with Perfuma. I'm your host, Perfuma. Let's start. Uh meditation is
not really the point of these videos. We'll begin with a deep cleansing breath. Seriously,
this is supposed to be used for new recruits. But it is. The Plumerians like many in
It's Rainbow 2.0!
Now, this is a fine mess we're in.
Huh?
That won't do.
Rainbow Cools Palace?
Activate!
Ah yes!
Now that's two scabbings with one bird!
You rockin' pal sunstones here to shine!
Watch out Sunstone, it's dangerous in here!
Not if you practice home safety!
Don't slip up, clear objects off the stairs!
Foul shot!
Make sure you cover your trash, or you might attract wild animals.
Come on, let's go.
Don't leave the water running.
It could flood your house.
Put protective covers on electrical outlets, especially when kids are around.
And most importantly, turn off motion smoothing on your TV.
Wow, everything looks so much better.
Heya!
I'm Smokey Quartz.
Nice to meet you.
I don't bother putting your socks back on because I'm about to knock them up again.
Now you guys can see exactly how I beat Jesse. This is a little trick I like to call. What the
dog? Wait, that's what it's called. You've had a chance to meet my new partner. Hey, I'm shut up.
It's cool to finally meet you. So you and Sadie have been dating for almost two months?
It's true.
You know, a lot of people say you don't really know someone until you've been stranded on
an island with them.
What?
People say that?
Yeah.
Well, we're gonna go grab some cake before we go on at seven.
Yeah!
But I woke up and I felt good, I said get me out of here, boom, Superman.
through operation warp speed.
Whether it's heroin, morphine, or today's synthetic opioids,
it all traces back to the same origin, the opium poppy.
Some of the earliest references to the plant
date back to 3,400 BC.
It was used by the ancient Greeks, Persians,
and the Egyptians.
A milky sap from the flower processed to produce opium,
which people would smoke to help them sleep.
relief pain. By the 7th century AD, opium made its way to China and East Asia. Fast forward to the
1700s, the British Empire begins smuggling opium into China through the East India Company. As a
result, opium addiction in China. China's attempts to outlaw the 1800s even sparked two wars with
the British. Opium use spread to the US during the California Gold Rush.
when thousands of Chinese workers came to the country.
Now back to morphine, the drug was first isolated from opium in 1803 to use as a painkiller.
In its most pure form, it's 10 times stronger than opium,
and is the base for synthetic opiates like codeine, oxy codeine, and fentanyl.
After thousands of soldiers became addicted to morphine during the Civil War,
English chemist Alder Wright developed heroin.
which was intended to be a safer alternative to morphine.
It was even marketed by the pharmaceutical company,
Bayer, as a cost suppressant for kids.
And by 1914, heroin and opiate addiction became such a problem
that the government passed the Harrison narcotics tax.
Been written off, counted out more times than I was ever able
Watched plans, fought through right in my hands
Watched life, redraw lines I didn't understand
They kept waiting on my collapse, hell I kept waiting too
But every year I buried a version of myself and came back somebody new
I'm no longer measured by what tries to bring me
Not by the losses, the scars are the way
by the things I keep building when I continue on folks in here report you
feel damn good at turning problems into options I verse one hidden and you choose
the door showing up some problems